{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Stephenson_(police_officer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/office",
    "object": "Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis",
    "human_readable": "Paul Stephenson (police officer) was the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.902941882610321,
            "question": "What city or region did Paul Stephenson oversee as Commissioner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8392142057418823,
            "question": "Was Paul Stephenson involved in law enforcement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7866396307945251,
            "question": "Who was Paul Stephenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7259001731872559,
            "question": "Were there any notable events during Paul Stephenson's time as Commissioner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5098978281021118,
            "question": "What does the title 'Commissioner of Police' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4666898846626282,
            "question": "What organization did Paul Stephenson lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45434778928756714,
            "question": "What were the responsibilities of a Commissioner of Police in that era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44307562708854675,
            "question": "What position did Paul Stephenson hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3590176999568939,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Paul Stephenson's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28343474864959717,
            "question": "How is Paul Stephenson remembered in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Stephenson (police officer) was the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_545_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Paul Stephenson's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_545_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Paul Stephenson hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_545_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the responsibilities of a Commissioner of Police in that era?",
            "html": "dbpedia_545_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_174.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_177.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_545_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provide various information about Sir Paul Robert Stephenson, including his birthdate, career as a police officer, and tenure as the Metropolitan Police Commissioner from 2009 to 2011. This suggests that the statement \"Paul Stephenson (police officer) was the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Sir Paul Robert Stephenson served as the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis from 2009 to 2011, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}